믿りハソ
Let's go!
We're the broken hearted people
Let's take the trip
We know you're there
To the heart of your mother
So that you can love women
Let's say the happy days
Shake it like a wave to me
Come on!
だまないで
You don't know baby, babe
お前のことさ
ラキラキパスボイ
遊んでみる風呂
You should know that I'm tonight
Love my you
You're the best you can find it
Just say, just say
Please kiss me side to side
あのセットで
まだやってるの
You're fine, you're fine
Winkされてた
So, so, so
踊れない
Let's get away
僕でつもりで乗せられた
Saturdays go on by
もう早く出して
だけできたなら
すれなきゃBaby, who are you?
殺しているのに
You gotta stop it, don't stop
もう行きながら
まるまる勝負
きてないから
出しちゃう
Thank you, I know that
That's easy
No, you need to eat my title
Rock, beat, help
I'm your idol
Super count, love
Bow come with the system
Live, sell your pop
Just like a play star
If you wanna dance
We're meant to so
Spose the time
We're meant to discusion
It's really not that
You better believe
You got the way you look
Sing with your guts
I'll be your model
Damn it, control
Want the heart, body
Sing with your back, do your back
Sing with your hip
How proud that's a baby
The model on the baby
We're not gonna care
What the player has to give it
The music of the boy
Keep them into the heart
And you're ready to beat
I guess this is how far
So, keep it
Come on
You're fine, you're fine
スピードがつく
Ah, B, B, B
もし気づかめたら
Dance it, dance it
Goo-oo-oo-oo
Kick it, dance, dance, dance, dance
Ain't no dream, take your round
踊っておくだけ
Side-talk, 置いて
Do your back
もし愛する
None-one
Kick it, dance, dance
Goo-oo-oo-oo
Baby, you are you
眩りに舞うだけ
眩りに舞いで
Do your back
こう気になるまでまで
Shyo-tie
Kick it, dance, dance, dance
好みで群れで
None-one
Dance it, do your back
もし愛する
Chicakete
Kick it, dance, dance
Goo-oo-oo-oo
Baby, you are you
欲しいって言うのいつか
そうね ドロンバー
大きなバルバルショー
もいてない
やっかあやっ
欲しいって言うの何か
もうに欲しいってドロンバー
あの子だろう
いつか何をしてた
すべていくわゆー
全部みんなに
欲しいって言うの何か
ドロンバー
あの子だってしかけてきたから
すべていくわゆー
欲しいって言うのに
欲しいって言うの何か
ドロンバー
大きなバルバルショー
もいてない
やっかあやっ
ドロンバー